

# JULIE MUZINA jmuzina@jmuzina.io | +1-216-538-7224 | Buffalo, NY 14202

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Full-Stack Engineer with 3+ years of experience designing, developing, and testing secure, well-documented, and user-friendly applications.

Experienced using Python, JavaScript, AWS cloud services, and SQL in public and private sector roles. Adept at collaborating across engineering and UX teams to improve the experience of all users.

#### **SKILLS**

- Full-Stack Web Development
- Business Intelligence & Data Visualization
- AWS Deployment & Cloud Services
- UX/UI Design & Cross-Functional Collaboration

#### **WORK HISTORY**

### **Software Engineer** | Canonical - Remote

04/2024 - CURRENT

- Maintain and enhance Vanilla Framework, supporting sites like ubuntu.com, used by millions of users globally.
- Architected and implemented design system testing suites, ensuring reliable deployments.
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams (Engineering, UX, Brand) to build consensus, solve problems, and drive user success.

**Software Developer** | Brooksource (Sherwin-Williams 11/2023 - 04/2024 Contractor) - Cleveland, OH (Hybrid)

- Supported a full-stack product inventory application used by a global salesforce. Architected & maintained cloud deployments & infrastructure.
- Led an overhaul of the CI/CD pipeline, increasing deployment reliability & velocity for a global sales application.

**Software Developer** | Comsat Architects (NASA 07/2022 - 11/2023 Contractor) - Rocky River, OH

- Developed intuitive mission planning and data visualization applications for NASA, translating complex scientific requirements into user-friendly interfaces.
- Mentored 2 interns to rapidly become effective contributors.

IT Intern (ETL Developer) | Medical Mutual of Ohio - 05/2022 - 07/2022 Cleveland, OH (Hybrid)

• Built ETL pipelines with SSIS to migrate data from data lakes to warehouses, providing actionable intelligence for business analysis.

#### **EDUCATION**

Kent State University, Kent, OH

05/2022

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

- 3.86 GPA, Magna cum laude graduate
- Capstone Project: GPX Visualizer a full-stack web application for creatively visualizing athletic activity